제작 - 네이트 드라마 24 자막팀
http://club.nate.com/24
1x02 Eric's Birthday
Aug 30, 1998 on FOX
저 여자들이 후터빌에
산다는 게 거슬리지 않냐?
hooterville : 젖소부인촌
Does it bother anybody else
that these women live in Hooterville?
엄밀하게 말해서 페티코트 환승역은
후터빌에서 오는 길에 있어
Petticoat Junction: TV 시리즈
Uh, technically, 'Petticoat Junction'
is down the track from Hooterville.
그럼 저 여자들이 후터빌에서 오는
길에 산다는 게 거슬리지 않냐?
Okay, does it bother anybody else
they live down the track from Hooterville?
It bothers me that they bathe
in the town water tank.
난 저 사람들이 동네 물탱크에서
목욕하는 건 신경쓰여
그것도 개랑 같이
With the dog...
마시는 물이 아니잖아
기차에 들어가는 물이야
It isn't the drinking water.
It is the water for the train.
그래도 벌거벗은 여자 3명에
개는 너무해
It's still three naked women
with a dog.
난 후터빌의 개가 되고 싶어
I want to be the Hooterville dog!
나 내려간다
You-hoo!
Coming down...
신경쓰지 마라
Now don't mind me.
빨래 좀 넣으려고 왔단다
I'm just putting some clothes in.
에릭, 네 생일에 이 옷
입으면 될 거 같구나
Eric, honey, I thought you could
wear this on your birthday.
좋잖아, 이거 입으면
얼마나 잘 생겨 보인다고
It's nice,
you look so handsome in it.
제 생일에 왜 잘 차려
입어야 하는데요?
Why would I want to dress nice
on my birthday?
니 생일이야?
It's your birthday?
오, 네 생일에 무슨 일이
생길지도 모르는 거잖니
Oh, you never know what's going to
happen on your birthday...
엄마, 엄마!
Mom. Mom!
생일 파티 열지 마세요
Do not throw a party for me.
아이고, 톱스타님
말하는 것 좀 보게
Oh well, listen to Mr. Popularity.
내가 무슨 파티라도
열 것처럼 말하는구나
Like I have time
to plan you a party.
어...
그런데 말이다
Oh, um, by the way, uh,
대학에 간 로리 누나가
주말동안 집에 온다는 구나
your sister Laurie is coming home
from college for the weekend.
특별한 이유는 없고
그냥 오는 거야
No special reason,
she just is.
너한테 파티 열어주시나봐
그것도 깜짝파티로
Well, you're getting a party
and best of all it's a surprise!
도나가 너보다 나이가
많은 걸 이제 알았네
I just realized
Donna's older than you.
겨우 1달 차인데 뭐
Only by a month.
에릭, 잘 됐다
Good for you Eric!
뭐가 잘 돼?
Good for me what?
우리나라에서는 연상의 여자랑
사랑하는 게 행운이거든
In my country, it is good luck to
fall in love with an older woman.
페즈! 페즈!
Fez...Fez!
가축도 데리고 온단 말야
No, they come with life-stock.
토퍼 그레이스 (에릭 포먼)
밀라 커니스 (재키 벅하트)
애쉬튼 커쳐 (마이클 켈소)
대니 메스털슨 (스티븐 하이드)
로라 프레폰 (도나 핀씨오티)
윌머 발더라마 (페즈)
데브라 조 러프 (키티 포먼)
커트우드 스미스 (레드 포먼)
타냐 로버츠 (미지 핀씨오티)
돈 스탁 (밥 핀씨오티)
That '70s Show 자막팀
싱크, 번역 : 김은경(toy69@nate)
수정 : 김현정(fuchs@nate)
That '70s Show 자막팀
대본수정, 싱크 : 김은경(toy69@nate)
- 안녕히 주무셨어요?
- 잘 잤니?
- Morning.
내가 꺼내줄게
I'll get it!
I'll get it.
저 안에 있는 거
감자칩 7봉지 맞죠?
Did I just see about seven bags
of potato chips in there?
세일하길래 샀다
They were on sale.
제발 파티 열지 마세요!
Please don't throw me a party!
파티 안 열 거다
I'm not throwing a party.
- 열어주지 말구려
- 안 그럴거예요
Don't give him one.
I'm not.
깜짝파티하기에는
나이가 너무 많아
He's too old
for a surprise party.
동감이에요
I'm agree with you.
- 그럼 소리 그만 질러
- 소리 지르는 거 아녜요
Then stop yelling.
I'm not yelling.
돈이 빡빡하다는 거 알고
큰 파티도 필요없어요
Look, I know money is tight,
so I don't want a big birthday.
돈이 빡빡한지는
내가 결정하는 거다
I'll decide when money is tight.
그래, 어떤 선물이 받고 싶으냐?
Now, what kind of gift do you want?
돈 걱정은 하지 마라
합리적인 선물이라면
Don't worry about the cost...
As long as it's reasonable.
그럼, 차에 달
카세트 플레이어요
Okay, I would like
a cassette player for the car.
8트랙 말고 카세트 플레이어요
8트랙은 싫어요, 아셨죠?
거의 차에나 달던 구식 카트리지
A cassette, not an eight-track.
No eight-track, okay?
왜 차에 처음부터 레코드 플레이어를
장착해 놓지 않는지 모르겠구나
You know, I don't know why they just
don't put record players in cars.
중요한 건 8트랙 플레이어는 안 된다는 거예요
The point is I don't want
an eight-track tape player.
그럼 안 사줄 거다
Then you won't get one.
오, 하지만 여보
하나 사달라잖아요
Oh, but honey he wants one.
아뇨, 8트랙 말고
플레이어가 갖고 싶어요
No, I want a tape player,
just not an eight-track.
델코사 제품으로 사주마
You'll get a Delco.
A genuine GM part
for your genuine GM car.
진짜 GM차에는
순정 GM부품을 써야지
델코 꺼일 필요도 없어요
음악 듣는 데 쓰는 것 뿐인데
It doesn't have to be a Delco.
It's just for music.
이런, 벌써 니가 잘못
생각하고 있는 거다
Oh now, see now,
there's your first mistake.
부품은 호환성 있는 걸
써야 한다, 에릭
Parts have to be
compatible, Eric.
그 차에 싸구려 기름
넣고 있는 건 아니겠지?
You're not burning cheap gas
in that car, are you?
그럼요, 아버지
No, sir.
그럼 나가 볼게요
Well, I'm going out.
오 오 얘야 저기
Oh, oh, good. Um...
가게에 가서 심부름
좀 해 주겠니
I want you
to run to the store for me.
케잌가루 큰 걸로 한 캔이랑
Get a large can of frosting and
fifteen small bags of M&Ms,
plain, not peanuts.
M&Ms 작은 거로 15봉지만 사오렴 땅콩 든 거 말고 그냥 M&Ms로
누나 줄 거란다
They're for your sister.
들킬 뻔했네요
That was close!
그래서?
So?
뭐?
What?
에릭 생일 선물로
뭐 줄건데?
What are you going to get Eric
for his birthday?
모르겠어
적당한 게 하나도 없어
I don't know.
Nothing seems right.
뭔가 특별한 걸 주고 싶은데
I want to give him
something special.
에릭이 너한테 키스했구나!
He kissed you!
쉬! 쉬!
Shh! Shh!
차에 타! 도나
얘기 좀 하게 차에 타
Get in the car! Donna,
get in the car so we can talk.
그래, 어떻게 된건데?
Okay, what happened?
재키, 이 얘기
너한테 안 할거야
Jackie, I'm not gonna talk
to you about this!
그럼 누구한테 할건데?
And who are you gonna talk to?
좋아
Okay.
런그렌 콘서트에서 돌아와서
차 본네트 위에 앉아 있었는데
We get home from the
Rundgren concert
and I'm sitting on
the hood of the car...
내가 키스했어!
And I kissed him!
찐하게 아님 뽀뽀?
French or American?
내가 너한테 이 얘길
왜 하고 있는지 모르겠다
I can't believe
I'm talking to you about this.
얘들아, 그만해
Guys, No...
좋아, 그래서
Okay! So.
난 평생을 에릭 옆집에 살았어
우린 서로 못하는 말이 없다구
Look, I’ve lived next door
to Eric my entire life
and we talk about
everything together.
같은 음악을 좋아하고
둘 다 패커즈팀 팬이야 위스콘신주 그린베이의 프로미식축구팀
We love the same music,
we love the Packers.
그런데 내가 키스하고
모든 게 달라졌어
Then I kissed him and
everything changed.
이제는 에릭이 애인인지
가장 친한 친구인지 모르겠어
And now I don’t know if he’s my
boyfriend, or if he’s my best-friend .
걔가 애인이면
친구를 잃는 거고
If he’s my boyfriend,
I'd lose my best friend.
내가 망쳐버리면 친구과 애인
모두들 잃는 거고
If I screw it up, I lose my
best-friend and my boyfriend.
이제는 생일 선물도 줘야 하는데
어떤 걸로 줘야...
Now I have to give him
this gift and I don’t…
도나, 도나!
Donna. Donna!
해결했어
I’ve solved it.
이걸로 해...
향기나는 초
Get him… a scented candle.
향기나는 초?
A scented candle?
실용적이면서도
로맨틱 한거야
It’s practical and romantic.
그렇고 말고
Oh yeah!
마지막에 내가 공을 가졌으니까
내가 이겼어!
I had the ball last, I win!
아니야, 니가 이긴 게 아니야
No, you didn’t win.
맞아, 공을 마지막에
가졌으니까...
Yes, I had the ball last and…
세상에
Holy Mother!
안녕, 로리
Hello Laurie.
안녕, 켈소
Hello Kelso,
하이드
Hyde.
저 여신님은 누구야?
Who is the goddess?
저 여신님은 에릭의 누나야
The goddess is Eric’s sister.
여신이 아니야
She’s not a goddess,
나한테나 어울리는
창녀과라고 봐야지
she’s more the earth mother whore
type which works for me.
로리
Laurie.
에릭
Eric.
옷 좀 입지 그래?
Shouldn’t you put
some clothes on?
왜?
Why?
좀 춥지 않아?
Aren’t you a little cold?
아니, 사실 더운데?
No, in fact, I’m hot.
오 그래? 그럼
윗층에 올라가지 그래?
Oh, well then
why don’t you go upstairs?
청바지가 건조기에서
나오는 거 기다리고 있어
I am waiting for my jeans
to come out of the dryer.
내 일에 참견 말았으면 하는데
And I want you
to stay off my case.
금방 끝날거야
It’ll only take me a minute.
켈소는 그렇게 오래
견디지 못할 거 같은데
I don’t think Kelso is
gonna last that long!
안 됐네, 밑에 홀딱 벗은 건
아닌 것 같거든
Too bad. It’s not like
I’m completely naked under this.
팬티는 입고 있지, 보여?
I’m wearing underwear, see?
- 오
- 아이...
- Oh.
- Ai!
해변이었으면
신경도 안 쓸거면서
If we were at the beach,
you wouldn’t even notice me.
해변이었으면
켈소는 당장 물에 들어가겠지
If we were at the beach,
Kelso would be in the water right now.
너 이제 차 있다며
So I understand
you have the wagon now.
내일 밤에 필요하니까
빌려줬으면 해
I want to borrow it
tomorrow night. I need it.
좋아, 부탁 하나 들어줘
Okay, but I need a favor.
부탁? 싫은데
For you? I don’t think so.
제발
Come on.
엄마한테 내가 깜짝파티 하기에는
너무 나이가 많다고 말해 줘
Look, just tell mom I’m
too old for surprise parties.
하지만 넌 애기고 엄마는
널 사랑하시잖아, 아가야
But you’re the baby and
Momma loves her baby.
그렇게 해주면
비스타 크루저 빌려줄게
If you do it, you can
borrow the Vista Cruiser.
밤새도록
All night.
밤새도록?
All night?
좋아
Fine!
그럼 약속했다
Then it’s a deal. Baby.
아가야
우후후후후!
Wouhouhouhouhou!
오~ 예!
Oh! Yeah!
니네 누나가 나랑 하고 싶대
Your sister wants me!
나한테 꼬리치는 거 봤지?
I mean, you saw her
coming on to me right?
나둬 봐
Let him go!
기억나? 내가
'안녕, 로리' 하니까
Remember?
I said ‘Hello Laurie’and Laurie said...
안녕, 켈소
Hello Kelso-I’m waiting-
and I want you-baby-take me-now
난 기다리고 있어
너랑 하고 싶어
자기
하자
지금
I need it-bad-I need it-all night
하고 싶어
정말
밤새도록
And Momma loves her, baby.
엄마가 예뻐해줄게, 자기~
나 밑에 홀딱 벗었고
I’m completely naked under this-
and-I’m hot-for-you-Kelso!
무지 달아올랐어, 켈소!
뭐야?
What?
못봤어?
You didn’t see it?
마당에서 꺼져!
Get out of the yard!
그래
So, how’s your friend Janice?
네 친구 제니스는
어떻게 지내니?
임신했어요
Pregnant.
저런, 좋은 애였는데
어쩌다 그렇게 됐니?
Oh, she was such a nice girl,
how does that happen?
그건...
Well, first the egg travels down
the fallopian tube to the uterus
먼저 난자가 나팔관을
따라 자궁으로 이동해서
자궁 벽에 착상한 다음
where it attaches to the wall…
에릭, 그만둬라
Eric, for God’s Sakes, that’s
no language for a woman to hear!
여자가 들을 만한
말이 아니구나!
괜찮아요, 아빠, 저도
나팔관이 뭔지 알아요
It’s okay Red,
I know what a fallopian tube is.
I think mom does too.
엄마도 아실 꺼에요
난 내 아들이 이런 말을
입에 담는 게 싫구나
Well, I just don’t like my little boy
bandying those words about.
넌 아직도 엄마에겐
아가란다
You’re still my baby!
고마워요, 엄마
Thanks mom… Laurie!
누나?
누나 그만 쳐다보고
당근이나 먹어라
Quit staring at your sister
and eat your carrots.
아 맞다, 에릭이 파티 열기에는
너무 나이가 많다고 말해달랬어요
Oh yeah, Eric wanted me to tell you
that he thinks he’s too old for a party.
Keys.
차 키 내놔!
파티 안 연다니까!
로리, 입 조심해라
There’s no party!
Laurie, loose lips!
로리, 지금 생각났는데
비스타 크루저는 못 빌려주겠어
Oh Laurie, I just remembered,
I can’t loan you the Vista Cruiser
난 니가 싫거든
on account of I hate you.
로리, 넌 비스타 크루저를
몰면 안 된다
Laurie, you’re not
driving the Vista Cruiser.
너무 낡아서 불안하거든
It’s old and undependable.
고장날 수도 있는데 그랬다가
지나가던 미친 놈한테 걸리면 어쩌겠어
It could break down
and you’d be at the mercy of
any maniac who came along.
에릭이야 상관없다만
That’s okay for Eric.
넌 토요타를 타거라
But you’re taking the Toyota.
아, 그리고...
Oh, and then here’s a twenty.
20달러 여기있다
기름값으로 충분할까요?
Will that cover gas?
그래 충분히 줘야지, 여보
모르니까 10달러 더 주세요
Oh well, it should. Honey, honey,
give her another ten just in case.
저도 기름값이
필요한 것 같은데요
Naw...I could probably
use some gas money.
그래? 뱁새가 황새 좇다
가랑이 찢어지지
Yeah. And if a frog had wings, he
wouldn’t bump his ass when he hops.
나가요, 나가!
Coming. I’m coming!
도나
Donna, Donna, it’s three am!
Are you crazy?
도나, 새벽 세 시잖아!
미쳤니?
미쳤나고?
Crazy?
Crazy in love with...you!
미치도록 사랑하지...
널!
너의 무엇이 날 이렇게 열정과
욕망으로 미치게 하는거지?
What is it about you that drives me
wild with passion and desire?
음.. 내가...
Well, I am seventeen now.
17살이 되어서 아닐까
입다물고 앉아 봐
Shut up and sit down!
생일 선물을 줘야겠어
I have to give you
your birthday present.
더 이상 기다릴 수 없어
It can’t wait any longer.
눈 감아 봐
Close your eyes!
이게 내 생일 선물이야?
This is my birthday present?
아니, 그건 내 잠옷이야
No, that’s my nightgown.
내가 니 선물이야
I’m your present.
눈 떠 봐, 생일맞은 소년!
Open your eyes birthday boy!
놀랐지!
Surprise!
생일 아침 식사란다
이게 다야!
Birthday breakfast!
And this is it young man!
밤에 선물 몇 개 주고 끝이지!
A few gifts tonight, the end!
이젠 파티에 대해 마음이
변했어도 너무 늦었다
And it is too late to change
your mind about a party now
그러니 파티가 있을 거라고
생각하면 정말 실망할거다
so don’t think you’re getting one
or you will be sorely disappointed!
생일 축하한다
Happy birthday.
너도 알다시피...
You know, the lawn’s not
gonna cut itself!
잔디는 저절로 깎이는 게 아니다
고마워요 엄마, 아빠
Thanks mom, dad.
동생아
Hey little brother, nice tent!
텐트 잘 쳤구나
너희들이 여기서 뭐하고
있는 지 다 알아
Look, I know what you’re
all doing here.
무슨 소릴 하는거야?
What are you talking about, man?
언제나처럼 모여서
노는 것 뿐이야
We’re just hanging out like always
잘 차려 입었지만 딴 뜻이
있는 건 아니고
except we’re dressed nice
but that doesn't mean anything.
얘들아 음, 너희들이
뭘 좀 도와줬으면 하는데
Hi kids. Um, I need
your help with something.
재키, 도나, 마이클, 스티븐,
Jackie, Donna, Michael, Steven,
발음 이상한 젊은이!
young man with an accent!
도와주겠니?
에릭, 넌 아니다!
Could you give me a hand?
Not you Eric!
더 이상 못 참아!
God, I can’t take it!
- 하지만 전..
- 안 돼, 안 돼!
- But no...I...
- No. Noooo-!
에릭, 얘야
잠깐 올라와 주겠니?
Eric, Eric, honey, honey, could
you come up here for a second?
조용해라, 에릭이 온다!
Shut up, he’s coming!
놀랐지!
Surprise!!!
이런!
Wow, I mean...yeah!
제 말은...
야호!
8트랙 테이프 플레이어란다
It’s an eight-track tape player!
알아요
I see that!
니가 갖고 싶어하던 거지!
Just what you asked for!
니가 너무 갖고 싶어하길래
적어 뒀었단다!
You made such a big deal about it,
I wrote it down!
카세트 테이프네!
Cassettes! Great, thanks Hyde.
잘 됐다, 고마워, 하이드
천만에
You’re welcome!
오, 얼른 8트랙 플레이어에
넣고 틀어보자!
Oh! Let’s put them in the eight-track
and play them!
뜨거운 면도거품 만드는 기계잖아
Hey! It’s a hot shave dispenser!
너한텐 앞으로도 필요없을 거야
아주 아주 오랫동안
Oh! He won’t need that for a long time!
A long, long time!
아니죠, 필요할거에요
다 큰 성인인 걸요
Of course, he will!
He’s almost like a man!
나도 줄 게 있어
I got you something.
안 돼!
No! Donna help me find my purse.
NOW!
도나, 지갑 찾는 것
좀 도와 줘!
당장!
재키, 지갑 가져오지도
않았잖아
Jackie, you didn’t even
bring a purse!
바보야! 남자애들 앞에서
에릭한테 선물주면 안 돼!
Duh! You can’t give him your present
in front of his guy friends!
하지만 나도 그
친구들 중 한 명인데
I am one of his guy friends.
도나, 이 선물에
내가 얼마나 신경썼는데
Look Donna, I have put a lot of
thought into this gift.
제발 망치지 마
Please do not wreck
this for me!
미안해, 내가 너무
이기적이었나봐!
I’m sorry. I guess
I was being selfish!
괜찮아
It’s okay.
자, 우리는 사라져 줄 시간이군
Okay, it’s time we disappeared.
뭐라고요? 여보, 여보
파티가 이제 시작했는데요
What? Honey, honey,
the party just started.
그러니 그게 우리가 밥네
집으로 가는 이유지
I know, that’s why we’re
going over to Bob’s.
전 에릭에게 파티를 열어주고
싶었고... / 열어줬잖아
- Well, I wanted to give Eric a party
- And you did.
개판 쳐놓으면 네놈들
모두 다 외출금지다!
You make a mess,
you’re all grounded.
요 꼬맹이 녀석들
You darn kids.
케찹이나 다른 게
떨어지면요?
You know, what if they run out of
ketchup or something?
갑시다!
Let’s go!
저기 빵도 더 있고 딜맛 피클이
싫거든 달콤한 맛도 있단다
dill : 미나리과 식물 향료
Okay, well, we have more buns and
sweet pickles if you don’t like the dill.
더 있고 싶지만 난 간다
Okay, I’d love to stay but I’m leaving.
저기, 맥주 좀 사다주면
두 배로 돈 줄게
Hey, buy us some beers,
we’ll pay double.
너 정말 맥주만 있으면 이 같잖은
파티가 좀 나아질 거라고 생각하는 거니?
Do you really think that beer will
make your little party better?
- 당연하지
- 그럼!
- Yeah.
- Yes!
내가 승낙하면 너희 어린 것들이
어른 기분을 낼 수 있겠지만
I admit it would give you
young people a sense of maturity,
그건 착각인데다
해선 안 될 일이지
but it would be a false maturity
and that would be wrong.
그럼 안 해 줄거야?
So you’re not gonna do it?
물론 안 해주지!
Of course not.
난 법적 성인 친구들이랑 맥주를
통으로 놓고 먹는 파티에나 가야 겠다.
Now I’m going off to join my legal
friends at a party, with a keg. Bye.
안녕
저, 로리
So, Laurie,
파티를 어디서 하는데?
이따가 들를지도 몰라서
where is the party, you know,
maybe we’ll cruise by later.
꿈깨셔, 바보야
In your dreams, you idiot.
어때, 니들도 똑똑히 봤지?
Okay, you guys had to see that!
'4'가 세 개야!
잘됐어
Three fours! I need them.
밥은 야치를 아주 잘 해요
Yatzi :주사위를 이용한 알파벳 게임
Bob is very good at Yatzee!
앗, 술 진열장!
Huh, the liquor cabinet!
잠궜어!
It’s locked!
비상사태가 생기면요?
What if there’s an emergency?
전화할거야
They’ll call.
감자칩 다 먹으면요?
What if they run out of chips?
굶겠지!
They’ll starve!
톰 콜린스나 한잔 해야지, 레드?
진 베이스의 칵테일
I’m gonna fix myself
a Tom Collins… Red?
난 됐고 키티나 한잔 주게
No, Kitty needs one.
너무 걱정돼요, 오 세상에
로리가 가고 있어요!
Well, I'm just so worried.
Oh My Lord! Laurie’s leaving!
여보, 그 애는 대학생이잖아
걔네들이랑 놀고 싶겠어?
Oh Honey, she’s in college, she
doesn’t want to hang around with them!
아무래도
전화를 해봐야 겠어요
Well, maybe I should
make a call, just in case…
여보
Kitty,
대체 무슨 일이 있겠어?
what could happen?
무슨 일이 있겠냐고요?
What could happen?
많은 일이 있을 수 있죠!
Well, plenty could happen!
많은 일이요!
Oh, Plenty!
자 이제 어른들이 갔으니
얼마든지 나쁜 짓 해도 돼!
Now that the adults are gone,
we can be as bad as we want!
에릭한테 성병 옮겨주고
싶은 사람?
Who wants to give Eric
a venereal disease?
이것봐, 컵받침이야!
Hey look, coasters!
컵받침따윈 없애버려!
Forget coasters!
제발 얘들아, 엄마는 이유가
있어서 받침을 놓아두셨을거야
Please fellas, my mom put out
coasters for a reason!
마시던 컵을 가구에
직접 놓아야지
I think I’m gonna put my drink
directly on the furniture.
그렇게 해야
자국이 남으니까!
That way, it will leave a ring!
안 돼! 내가 왜 엄마한테
계셔달라고 하지 않았을까?
Noooo! Why, oh why,
didn’t I beg my mother to stay?
조용히 해
멍청한 미국인아!
Quiet you silly American!
I am making a long-distance call
on your parent’s phone!
너의 부모님 전화로
장거리 전화하고 있잖아
하지만 그건 염치없는 짓이야
But that’s immoral!
하! 어딘지 말할 수는 없지만
우리나라에서는
Hah! In my country, of whereever
it is I am from, I can never tell,
염치는 기분좋게 노는데
방해만 돼
morals get in the way
of a good dirty time.
우선 감자칩 좀 먹어야겠다
But first, I need to
eat some chips.
뭐야? 다 먹었어?
What? Out of chips?
나 화났어!
뭔가 쏴버려야겠다!
Now I am mad!
I must shoot something!
호보 인형만은 안 돼!!!
Not the littlest hobo!!!!
안 돼!!!!!!!
WHY???!!!
당신이 과민반응하는 거야
You’re overreacting!
오 키티, 우리 발레리가 학교 때문에
집을 떠났을 때 저도 그랬어요
Oh Kitty, when Valerie went off
to school, I felt the same way…
하지만 이 작은 시집이
도움이 됐지요
But this little book
of poems helped me.
제목이
'빈 둥지로부터의 시'에요
It’s called
'Verses From An Empty Nest'
길 잃은 작은 새에 대한
시를 읽어주구려 / 네, 그러죠
Read her that one about the little bird
that lost its way. / Oh Yeah.
한 때는 노래했던 작은 새, 이제는 날개가
부러진 채 혼자 있네 / 오 저런!
The little bird that once did sing, Is
now alone with broken wing. / Oh God!
네, 듣기 좋군요
Yup, that sounds nice.
더 마셔야겠어요
I need a refill.
- 여보, 평소에는 한 잔만 마시잖아
- 오늘은 두 잔 마셔야겠어요
- But honey, usually you only drink one
- Well, tonight I’m having two.
현관에서 기다려
내가 에릭을 데려올게
Wait on the porch
and I’ll get Eric.
밖은 깜깜한데
It’s dark out there.
어차피 초를 줄거잖아!
And you’re giving him
a candle. Yeah!
여기, 성냥
Here, matches.
초를 켜고 싶지 않을지도 몰라
He might not want to light it.
그런 소리 하지마
생각도 말고!
Don’t say that! Don’t even think it!
선물을 뜯어보면 멋지다거나
뭐 그런 말을 할거야
Now, when he opens it,
he’ll say cool, or something
그 때 이런 표정을 지어
and then you give him a look,
like this.
그래, 도나가 뭘 줬니?
So, what did you get
from Donna?
아직 아무것도
Nothing yet.
아~
Ahh!
정말 큰 선물인가보다!
Maybe it’s the big gift!
내말은 정말 '큰 선물' 말야
You know, the really big gift!
내가 말하는 '큰 선물'이
뭔지 다들 알지?
You guys know what I’m saying
when I say the big gift, right?
그래, 알아
Yeah, we got it.
그리고 우리도 그 선물 받았지
And we got it.
난 여기 출신이 아닌데도
무슨 말인지 알아!
I’m not even from here
and I got it!
저기 에릭
도나가 현관에서 기다려
Oh Eric,
Donna’s on the porch.
에릭이 '큰 선물' 받으러 간다!
He’s getting the big gift!
아, 향기나는 초네!
정말 멋지다!
Oh, a scent candle!
This is very cool!
아, 아무것도 아닌데 뭐
Oh, it’s nothing.
너 괜찮니?
Are you okay?
어, 그래...괜찮아, 어
Oh, I’m fine! Yeah.
너 아프거나 이상해 보여
’Cause you, you had a look like
you might be sick or something.
그냥 바보짓 한번 해 본거야
I am just being completely stupid.
어, 그건 내 전문인데
Hey, that’s my job!
선물 걱정을 많이 했어
I was worried about the gift.
왜? 진짜 멋진 선물인데
성냥이 있다면 켰을거야
Why? This is a very cool gift.
I’d light it if I had matches.
오, 여기
Oh, here.
넌 모든 걸 생각하는구나
You thought of everything.
음, 생일 축하해
Well, Happy Birthday.
오오오오오!
Ooohhhhh…
이것 좀 봐요, 오오!
Look at this… oohhh,
여기에 초를 내 놓을
생각은 못했네
We never thought to put a candle out
here. Ohh, it is just so romantic!
오, 정말 낭만적이구나!
자, 갑시다
여기선 볼 게 없어요
Let’s. Let’s keep moving,
there’s nothing to see out here.
고마워요, 고마워요 아빠
Thanks, thanks dad.
우린 침실에 초 있는데, 그렇죠?
Oh, we have candles
in the bedroom, don’t we?
최종수정: 김현정(fuchs@nate)
지금이다
에릭이 할 거야!
This is it, he’s going for it!
하하...에릭 생일이니까
도나가 먼저 키스해야지
Huh Huh. It’s his birthday,
she should kiss him first.
저번에 했어
She did it last time!
뭐라고?
What?
아무 것도 아냐!
입 다물고 보기나 해
Nothing!
Shut up and watch.
어서 포먼, 해!
Come on Forman, go for it!
문이 열려 있거든?
다 들려
The door is open,
we can hear you…
다 보여!
We can see you!
키스하고 있니?
Is he kissing her?
아무도 못 보고 있잖아, 페즈
None of us can see them, Fez.
에릭, 키스하고 있니?
Eric, are you kissing her?
자유배포 / 수정금지
네이트 드라마 24 자막팀
http://club.nate.com/24
자유배포 / 수정금지
네이트 드라마 24 자막팀
http://club.nate.com/24